(Sheldon:)in which Marty and Doc Brown
ever use the time machine
(Sheldon:)to travel to 2015.
(Sheldon:)Therefore,
(Sheldon:)in the new timeline,
(Sheldon:)Marty and Doc never brought
the time machine...
W-Wait.
Is "brought" right?
(Sheldon:)Marty and Doc never
had have had brought?
(Leonard:)I don't know.
You did it to me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, I'm going with it.
(Sheldon:)Marty and Doc never
had have had brought
(Sheldon:)the time machine to 2015.
(Sheldon:)That means 2015 Biff could also
(Sheldon:)not had have had brought
the almanac to 1955 Biff.
(Sheldon:)Therefore, the timeline in which
1955 Biff gets the almanac
(Sheldon:)is also the timeline
(Sheldon:)in which 1955 Biff
never gets the almanac.
And not just "never gets."
(Sheldon:)Never have, never hasn't,
never had have hasn't.
(Raj:)He's right.